A Guide to the Cary Reich papers FA1275
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Interview Transcripts and Subject Files, undated; 1; 12 Cubic Feet
  - Jacob Underhill Interview (Box 4, Folder 147)
    National affairs writer for Newsweek magazine and later assistant press secretary for Governor Nelson Rockefeller during the 1964 and 1968 presidential campaigns and the 1966 New York gubernatorial campaign.
  - Jack Vandervort Interview (Box 4, Folder 148)
    Campaign aide for Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Edward Van Ness Interview (Box 4, Folder 149)
    Worked on various health and human services issues in the Program Office and the New York State Health Department, including drug addiction, Medicaid, and Governor Nelson Rockefeller's push for universal health insurance.
  - Andrew Von Hirsh Interview (Box 4, Folder 150)
    Aide to Senator Charles Goodell, a Republican from New York who was appointed by Governor Nelson Rockefeller to fill the Senate seat following the assassination of Senator Robert F. Kennedy.
  - Robert Wagner Interview (Box 4, Folder 151)
    A Democrat who served as mayor of New York from 1954 to 1965.
  - John Walsh Interview (Box 4, Folder 152)
    Worked as an assistant attorney general prior to Nelson Rockefeller's tenure and then served in Governor Rockefeller's administrations in as an assistant appointments officer and advance man.
  - Edward Warburg Interview, 1982 March 30 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    Philanthropist and friend of Nelson Rockefeller. He served on the board of trustees at the Museum of Modern Art, 1932-1958, and was a trustee and organizer of MoMA's film library. He was also vice director for public affairs of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1971-1974. In addition, Warburg was a co-founder of the American Ballet and the School of American Ballet.
  - F. Clifton White Interview (Box 4, Folder 154)
    Political consultant and campaign manager for Republican party and New York Conservative party candidates. He was also a leader of the Draft Goldwater Committee, 1961-1964.
  - Charles Widmayer Interview (Box 4, Folder 155)
    Dartmouth classmate of Nelson Rockefeller.
  - J. Walker Wiggin Interview (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Nadia Williams Interview, 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 157-158)
    A member of Nelson Rockefeller's staff at the Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs (CIAA) and then the U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (HEW).
  - Malcolm Wilson, Interview 1 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    Lieutenant Governor of New York during all four of Nelson Rockefeller's terms as Governor, 1959 to 1973. When Rockefeller resigned in 1973, Wilson succeeded him into office. He lost election to the office in 1974. He had started in public service in the New York State Assembly from 1939 to 1958.
  - Malcolm Wilson, Interview 2 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Malcolm Wilson, Interview 3 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Jerry Wolfgang Interview (Box 4, Folder 162)
    An advance man for Nelson Rockefeller's gubernatorial campaigns as well as for Governor Rockefeller's 1969 fact-finding mission to Argentina that looked into the embattled military government of Juan Carlos Ongania.
  - Albert and Virginia Callan Interview (Box 4, Folder 163)
    Albert Callan was a Columbia County (New York) Republican leader, and Virginia Callan was a gubernatorial aide to Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Alexander (Sam) Aldrich Interview, 1982 November 15 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    Cousin of Nelson Rockefeller who served as a gubernatorial advisor.
  - Edward Koch Interview (Box 4, Folder 165)
    Three-term Democratic mayor of New York from 1978 to 1989 who earlier served as a member of the U.S. House of Representatives, 1969 to 1977.
  - Lloyd Free Interview (Box 4, Folder 166)
    Political pollster who conducted surveys for Nelson Rockefeller's various campaigns.
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 9 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Richard Rosenbaum Interview (Box 4, Folder 168)
    Monroe County (NY) Republican chair, 1968 to 1970; New York State Supreme Court justice, 1970 to 1972; and New York Republican State Committee chair from 1973 to 1977.
  - Henry Diamond Interview (Box 11, Folder 169)
    Environmental lawyer and New York's first Commissioner of Environmental Conservation. He other roles included Laurance Rockefeller associate; Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commissioner; 1960 and 1968 NAR Presidential campaign advisor; Adirondacks Park Commissioner.
  - Margot Lindsay Interview (Box 4, Folder 170)
    Served on the Republicans for Progress group and the Draft Rockefeller movement in the 1968 Presidential campaign.
  - Franklin Lindsay Interview (Box 4, Folder 171)
    Consultant who advised Nelson Rockefeller regarding the Open Skies program during Rockefeller's service in the Eisenhower administration as Special Assistant to the President.
  - Paul Curran Interview (Box 4, Folder 172)
    Member of the New York State Assembly and then chair of the New York State Commission of Investigation.
  - Bill Watts Interview (Box 4, Folder 173)
    Director of the Office for Urban Innovation under for Governor Nelson Rockefeller in the late 1960s. Watts then was staff secretary of Presdient Richard Nixon's National Security Council for 18 months before resigning to protest planned military operations in Cambodia.
  - Milton Gwirtzmann Interview (Box 4, Folder 174)
    Advisor and speech writer for John, Robert, and Edward Kennedy.
  - Joseph Canzeri Interview (Box 4, Folder 175)
    Advance man for Governor Nelson Rockefeller, and later president of Greenrock Corporation.
  - Richard Nathan Interview (Box 4, Folder 176)
    Advisor to Governor Nelson Rockefeller and, later director of the Rockefeller Institute of Government.
  - David Goldberg Interview (Box 4, Folder 177)
    Political consultant
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 7 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Harold Stassen Interview (Box 4, Folder 179)
    As delegate at the conference that established the United Nations in 1945, Stassen was one of eight Americans who signed the UN Charter. (Nelson Rockefeller attended as well). Stassen then served in the adminstration of President Dwight D. Eisenhower for 5 years and unsuccessfully sought the Republican nomination for President 9 times between 1948 and 1988.
  - George Romney Interview (Box 4, Folder 180)
    Governor of Michigan in the 1960s, Romney ran unsuccessfully for the Republican presidential nomination in 1968. He later served as U.S. Secretary of Housing and Urban Development in the Nixon administration.
  - Bruce Gyory Interview (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - John Gillies Interview (Box 5, Folder 182)
    An aide at IBEC and for Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Robert Bennett Interview (Box 5, Folder 183)
    Superintendent of the New York State Executive Mansion while Nelson Rockefeller was Governor.
  - Susan Herter Interview (Box 5, Folder 184)
    Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs office; U.S. Department of State associate; Museum of Modern Art staff; chief of staff in U.S. Vice President's office
  - Edward Kresky, Interview 1 and Interview 2 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    Gubernatorial aide for Nelson Rockefeller.
  - Ted Van Dyk Interview (Box 5, Folder 186)
    Senior aide to Vice President Hubert Humphrey; author.
  - Alfred D. Lerner and Joseph Kunzeman Interview (Box 5, Folder 187)
    Lerner was a member of the New York State Assembly for parts of Queens County in the early 1960s, and Kunzeman was also a member of the Assembly for Queens County during the 1960s.
  - Warren Anderson Interview (Box 5, Folder 188)
    New York state senator.
  - John Burns Interview (Box 5, Folder 189)
    Mayor of Binghamton, New York, in the 1950s and early 1960s, who then served as New York State Democratic chair during the 1960s.
  - D. Clinton Dominick III Interview (Box 5, Folder 190)
    Member of the New York State Assembly and then a New York State senator from Newburgh.
  - Richard Kuhnen Interview (Box 5, Folder 191)
    Republican chair from Broome County, New York.
  - Carl Spad Interview (Box 5, Folder 192)
    New York State Appointments Officer; State Chair of Young Republicans
  - Malcolm Wilson, Interview 4 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - F. Clifton White, Interview 2 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Thomas J. Mackell Interview (Box 5, Folder 195)
    New York State senator from Queens from 1955 to 1966, and then district attorney of Queens County from 1967 to 1973.
  - Joseph Boyd, Interview 2 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    Governor Nelson Rockefeller's Congressional liaison officer in Washington, DC. Boyd also served as the Governor's liaison to the New York State legislature.
  - Jack Bigel Interview (Box 5, Folder 197)
    Labor union consultant and negotiator.
  - Stephen Duggan Interview (Box 5, Folder 198)
    Classmate of Nelson Rockefeller at the Lincoln School in Manhattan.
  - Murray Gart Interview (Box 5, Folder 199)
    Journalist and Rockefeller campaign aide.
  - John J. McEnany Interview (Box 5, Folder 200)
    Head of the human resources department under Albany (New York) Mayor Erastus Corning.
  - Wilma Rogalin Interview (Box 5, Folder 201)
    Vice chair of the New York State Republican Committee and president of its Women's Federation.
  - Raymond Corbett Interview (Box 5, Folder 202)
    Legislative director of the New York AFL-CIO.
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 8 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Al Abrams Interview (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Edward Teller Interview (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Sheldon Stark Interview (Box 5, Folder 206)
    Classmate of Nelson Rockefeller at the Lincoln School in Manhattan and Dartmouth College.
  - Guy Graves Interview (Box 5, Folder 207)
    New York state Republican committee leader from Schenectady in the 1960s.
  - Charles Lanigan Interview (Box 5, Folder 208)
    New York state Republican chair in the 1960s.
  - Henry Kissinger, Interview 1 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    Longtime advisor to Nelson Rockefeller: Director of his Special Studies Project for the Rockefeller Brothers Fund in the late 1950s, foreign policy advisor to Nelson Rockefeller's presidential campaigns, and later as U.S. Secretary of State in the Nixon and Ford Administrations.
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 3 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 3 (Box 12, Folder 210a)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 4 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 4 (Box 12, Folder 211a)
  - Stuart Spencer Interview (Box 5, Folder 212)
    Political aide for Nelson Rockefeller during the 1964 Republican presidential primaries.
  - William Rusher Interview (Box 5, Folder 213)
    Publisher of National Review magazine who helped found the Conservative Party of New York in 1961 and the American Conservative Union in 1964. He worked on Senator Barry Goldwater's successful 1964 campaign for the Republican presidential nomination.
  - John Deardourff Interview (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Arnold Fisher Interview (Box 5, Folder 215)
    Republican party chair of Madison County, New York.
  - Richard Dunham, Interview 2 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    Deputy budget director and then director of the budget for Governor Nelson Rockefeller. Dunham was also deputy director of the White House Domestic Council when Rockefeller was U.S. Vice President.
  - Daniel Mahoney Interview (Box 5, Folder 217)
    One of the founders of the New York Conservative Party in 1962.
  - George Humphreys Interview (Box 5, Folder 218)
    Deputy director of Governor Nelson Rockefeller's reelection campaign in 1970 and then appointed assistant Commissioner of Environmental Conservation for New York City Affairs.
  - Samuel Lefrak Interview (Box 5, Folder 219)
    Real estate investor who served on the New York State Traffic Safety Council and the Saratoga Springs Commission.
  - Moses Weinstein Interview (Box 5, Folder 220)
    Democratic member of the New York State Assembly in the 1960s and majority leader and from 1965 to 1968. In 1969, he was elected to the New York State Supreme Court.
  - Joseph McGovern Interview (Box 5, Folder 221)
    Bond attorney who worked on the financing of the construction of the Empire State Plaza in Albany.
  - Perry Duryea Jr. Interview (Box 6, Folder 222)
    Republican member of New York State Assembly; served as Speaker of the Assembly from 1969 to 1973.
  - Richard Dunham Interview (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Al Roberts Interview (Box 6, Folder 224)
    Staff director of the New York State Assembly Ways and Means Committee and a member of the Albany Arts Council.
  - Robert M. Morgenthau Interview, 20 pages (Box 6, Folder 225)
    The 1962 Democratic nominee for Governor of New York, against whom Nelson Rockefeller won his second term in office.
  - Harold Jerry Interview (Box 6, Folder 226)
    Republican New York State senator in the early 1960s and, under Governor Nelson Rockefeller, director of the Office for Regional Development and then the first director of the Office of Planning Coordination.
  - Irwin Miller Interview (Box 6, Folder 227)
    Chair of the Rockefeller for President Commmittee during the 1968 presidential campaign.
  - Edwin Schwenk Interviews (Box 6, Folder 228)
    Republican Party chair of Suffolk County, New York, from 1967 to 1977.
  - Paul Nitze Interview (Box 6, Folder 229)
    Financial division director when Nelson Rockefeller was Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs for the Roosevelt administration during World War II.
  - Herbert Brownell Interview (Box 6, Folder 230)
    U.S. Attorney General during the first Eisenhower administration.
  - Joseph Margiotta, Interview 2 (Box 6, Folder 231)
    New York State Assembly member from Uniondale, 1966 to 1976, and then Nassau County (NY) Republican chair from 1968 to 1983.
  - Raymond Schuler Interview (Box 6, Folder 232)
    Instrumental in the creation of the New York Department of Transportation, Schuler served as the department's commissioner during Governor Nelson Rockefeller's final term.
  - Arthur Taylor Interview (Box 6, Folder 233)
    Former president of Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS), Taylor co-founded the Sarabam Corporation with Nelson Rockefeller in the late 1970s.
  - Hugh Carey Interview (Box 6, Folder 234)
    Democratic Governor of New York who beat Republican Malcolm Wilson (who served out Nelson Rockefeller's fourth term). Previously had served several terms in the U.S. House of Representatives.
  - Phil Donahue Show, Nelson Rockefeller appearance (Box 6, Folder 235)
    Material related to Rockefeller's appearance on show #11178.
  - Edward Kresky, Interview 3 (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Henry Diamond, Interview 2 (Box 11, Folder 237)
    Environmental lawyer and New York's first Commissioner of Environmental Conservation. His other roles included Laurance Rockefeller associate; Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commissioner; 1960 and 1968 NAR Presidential campaign advisor; Adirondacks Park Commissioner.
  - Robert Curcio Interview (Box 6, Folder 238)
    Suffolk County (NY) Republican chair.
  - Joseph Crangle Interview (Box 6, Folder 239)
    Erie County (NY) Democratic chair and then New York State Democratic chair.
  - Charles Percy Interview (Box 6, Folder 240)
    Republican from Illinois who served in the U.S. Senate from the 1960s to the 1980s. His daughter Sharon married Nelson Rockefeller's nephew Jay (John D. IV).
  - Matthew Troy Interview (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - William Vanden Heuvel Interview (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Ernest Curto Interview (Box 6, Folder 243)
    Republican member of the New York state assembly from Niagara County.
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 10 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Albert Hausbeck Interview (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Phelan Interview (Box 6, Folder 246)
    Aide to New York state Senate Majority Leader Earl Brydges.
  - William Seidman Interview (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Charles Webb, Interview 2 (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Charles Webb, Interview 1 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - William Dietel Interview (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Alan Miller Interview (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Albert Bowker Interview (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Donald Button Interview (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Oscar Lanford Interview (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - John Deardourff Interview (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - John Kingston Interview (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Paul Belica Interview (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Robert Douglass, Interview 2 (Box 11, Folder 258)
    Douglass served as Nelson Rockefeller's third Counsel to the Governor.
  - Gerald Ford Interview (Box 6, Folder 259)
    Ford was a Republican from Michigan who served as the 38th President of the United States. He nominated Nelson Rockefeller to fill the position of Vice President under the 25th Amendment of the U.S. Constitution.
  - David Rockefeller, Interview 3 (Box 11, Folder 260)
    Youngest brother of Nelson Rockefeller.
  - David Rockefeller, Interview 3 (Box 11, Folder 260a)
  - David Rockefeller, Jr. Interview (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Peter Paine Interview (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Robert Douglass, Interview 1 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Daniel Patrick Moynihan Interview (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Charles Rangel Interview (Box 6, Folder 265)
    Democratic New York State Assembly member from 1967 to 1970 and a member of the U.S. House of Representatives for the district including Harlem from 1971 to 2017. Governor Nelson Rockefeller endorsed Rangel for his 1968 reelection to the New York State Assembly.
  - Stephen Hopkins Interview (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - Hugh Morrow Interview with Kenneth Riland and other files (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Moses Weinstein Interview (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - Victor Gotbaum Interview (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Robert Armao Interview (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Henry Kissinger, Interview 2 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Roswell Perkins, Interview 4 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Ann Hevesi Interview (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - John Marchi Interview (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Clifton Wharton Interview (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Sylvester (Pat) Weaver Interview (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - James Emery Interview (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Jonathan Moore Interview (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 5 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 5 (Box 12, Folder 280a)
  - Enid Feist Interview (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Oscar Ruebhausen, Interview 3 (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Jack Germond Interview (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Barry Van Lare Interview (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Richard Parsons Interview (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Donald Zimmerman Interview (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - John Byron Interview (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - John Egan Interview (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Michael Whiteman Interview (Box 7, Folder 289)
    Served as Counsel to Governor Nelson Rockefeller during his third and fourth administrations.
  - Charles Urstadt Interview (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - John Sears Interview (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Percy Sutton Interview (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - James Casberry Interview (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Peter Wallison Interview (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Mark Rockefeller Interview (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - James Wallis Interview (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - David Belin Interview (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Roger Hooker Interview (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Rodman Rockefeller, Interview 2 (Box 12, Folder 299)
    Oldest child of Nelson and Mary Clark Rockefeller. Ran the International Basic Economy Corporation after his father divested his interest upon becoming the governor of New York.
  - Rodman Rockefeller, Interview 2 (Box 12, Folder 299a)
  - Richard Aldrich Interview (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Endicott Peabody Interview (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - William Bagley (Review) Interview (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - Wyatt Tee Walker Interview (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - William Brinton Interview (Box 7, Folder 304)
    Interview was conducted by phone rather than in person.
  - Peter Ogden Interview (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Lou Levine Interview (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Jay Coral Interview (Box 7, Folder 307)
    Conducted by phone rather than in person.
  - Gary Lee Interview (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - John Love Interview (Box 7, Folder 308A)
  - Donal O'Brien, Jr. Interview (Box 12, Folder 309)
  - Donal O'Brien, Jr. Interview (Box 12, Folder 309a)
  - James Kiepper Interview (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Richard Stewart Interview (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Jack Vandervourt, Interview 2 (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Senator John D. (Jay) Rockefeller IV Interview (Box 12, Folder 313)
    Nephew of Nelson Rockefeller. Served as Governor of West Virginia and then as a U.S. Senator from West Virginia.
  - Harold Haskell Interview (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Arthur Richardson Interview (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Stephen Berger Interview (Box 7, Folder 316)
  - Donald Rumsfeld, Interview 2 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    White House Chief of Staff and later Secretary of Defense during President Gerald Ford's administration.
  - Thomas Rosenberg Interview (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Robert Hartmann Interview (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Warren Weaver Interview (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Thomas Laverne Interview (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Vincent ToPany Interview (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Mildred Mattaheda Interview (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - James Cannon, Interview 2 (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Fergus Reid Interview (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Edward Logue Interview (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - William Kintner Interview (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Ogden Reid Interview (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Harold Albright, Interview 3 (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Lawrence Murray Interview (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Levitch and Lightfoot Interview (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Robert Stone Interview (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - John Hightower Interview (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Ted Parker Interview (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - Lois Wilson Interview (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - Abby Milton O'Neill Interview (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Abby Milton O'Neill Interview (Box 12, Folder 336a)
  - Michael Scelsi Interview (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Dorothy Miller Interview (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Laurence Roberts Interview (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - J. Richardson Dilworth Interview (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - J. Richardson Dilworth Interview (Box 12, Folder 340a)
  - Barber Conable Interview (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - Peter Berle Interview (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Martin Ives Interview (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - George Gilder Interview (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - Ernest Boyer Interview (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - Elizabeth Corning Interview (Box 8, Folder 346)
  - Ray Schuler Interview (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - John Gardner Interview (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign, 4 folders (Box 8, Folder 349-352)
  - State Liquor Authority - Liquor Scandal, 3 folders (Box 8, Folder 353-355)
  - Morhouse - State Liquor Authority (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - Morhouse - State Liquor Authority (Box 9, Folder 357-359)
  - Charles Mathias Interview (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Jason Gettinger Interview (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Sol Neil Corbin, Interview 2 (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Subject Files, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 363-364)
  - New York Governor, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 365-366)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) Interviews, 3 folders (Box 9, Folder 367-369)
    Nelson Rockefeller created IBEC in 1947 to promote "basic ecomonomies" in developing countries and thus encourage others in those countries to establish competitive businesses. Rockefeller served as president of IBEC until 1958, when he resigned to assume his duties as Governor of New York.
  - M. L. Whitney Interview (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Anne-Marie Rasmussen Interview (CLOSED FOLDER) (Box 12, Folder 371)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller (Box 9, Folder 372-373)
  - Children (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Governor (Box 9, Folder 375-377)
  - Governor (Box 10, Folder 378-379)
  - Special Studies, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 380-381)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign, 4 folders (Box 10, Folder 382-385)
  - Indexes (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Letters and Interviews (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Ballentyne Interview (Box 10, Folder 388)